Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010)
  - Subseries III.6 - Office of Development - Printed Matter, circa 1977-2011
    - Citibank Tennis Champions Tour, 1995 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 19)
    - 190th Anniversary Media Information Kit, 1996 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 20)
    - Brochure with Timeline, circa 1997 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 21)
    - Brochure Information, 1998 and 2000 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 22)
    - Literacy Initiative Brochure, 2000 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 23)
    - Halloween Party sponsored by Westchester Friends, 2000 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 1)
    - P.R. Fliers re: Children and GW, 2005 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 2)
    - NY Times Ad, 2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 3)
    - Mayor's Proclamation on Graham Windham Day, 2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial Ball, 2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 5)
    - 200th Anniversary Information Kit, 2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 6)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Brochures, 2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Fliers, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 8)
    - Handbook covers, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 9)
    - "Ever Think About Becoming a Professional Parent?" pamphlet, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 10)
    - "The Ultimate Investment" adoption flier and pamphlet, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 11)
    - Manhattan Center pamphlets, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 12)
    - Foster parent pamphlets: "Commit to Caring" and "Can You Provide a Home...", undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 13)
    - Family Day Care Pamphlets, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 14)
    - Primary Health Care Services pamphlet, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 15)
    - Advocacy Postcards, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 16)
    - Explanatory Pamphlet for Hastings Community Neighbors, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 17)
    - Family Service Center Pamphlets (Crown Heights), undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 18)
    - Early Childhood Packet, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Fliers, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 20)
    - "The Graham School - a Special Place for Your Special Children" pamphlet, undated (Offsite-box 58, Folder 21)
    - Christmas, 2007 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 22)
    - Holiday Season Donation Card, 2009 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 23)
    - Holiday Cards, 1991 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 24)
    - Christmas Card, 1993 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 25)
    - Christmas Cards, 1994 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 26)
    - Holiday Cards, 1997 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 27)
    - Holiday Cards, 1998 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Cards, 1999 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Ideas, 2000 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 30)
    - Graham Messenger - Alumni Newsletter, 1994 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 1)
    - Graham Messenger - Alumni Newsletter, 1995 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
    - Graham Messenger - Alumni Newsletter, 1996 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 3)
    - Graham Messenger - Alumni Newsletter, 1997 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 4)
    - Newsflash - Employee Newsletter, 1994 May (Offsite-box 59, Folder 5)
    - Newsflash - Employee Newsletter, 1994 June and July (Offsite-box 59, Folder 6)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1994 September (Offsite-box 59, Folder 7)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1994 November (Offsite-box 59, Folder 8)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1994 December (Offsite-box 59, Folder 9)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 January (Offsite-box 59, Folder 10)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 March (Offsite-box 59, Folder 11)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 April (Offsite-box 59, Folder 12)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 June (Offsite-box 59, Folder 13)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 July (Offsite-box 59, Folder 14)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 September (Offsite-box 59, Folder 15)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1995 October (Offsite-box 59, Folder 16)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1996 January (Offsite-box 59, Folder 17)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1996 March (Offsite-box 59, Folder 18)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1996 May (Offsite-box 59, Folder 19)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1996 July (Offsite-box 59, Folder 20)
    - Currents - Employee Newsletter, 1996 October (Offsite-box 59, Folder 21)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Spring/Summer, 1983 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 1)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Fall/Winter, 1983 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Spring/Summer, 1984 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Fall/Winter, 1984 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter", 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Spring/Summer, 1986 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 6)
    - "Graham Windham Newsletter" Winter/Spring, 1987 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 7)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1988 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 8)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Winter/Spring, 1988 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 9)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 1989 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 10)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Spring/Summer, 1990 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 11)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1990 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 12)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Spring/Summer, 1991 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 13)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1991 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 14)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Spring/Summer, 1992 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 15)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 16)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Spring, 1994 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 2)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Summer/Fall, 1994 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Fall/Winter, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 4)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Summer/Fall, 1995 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 5)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 1997 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 1998 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 7)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 1999 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2001 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 9)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2002 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 10)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2005 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 11)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Bicentennial Edition No. 1, 2006 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 12)
    - "Graham Windham Record" Bicentennial Edition No. 2, 2006 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 13)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2007 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 14)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2009 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 15)
    - "Graham Windham Record", 2011 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 16)
  - Subseries III.7 - Office of Development - Administrative Materials, 1983-2011 (bulk 1990-1996)
    The Office of Development at Graham Windham is responsible for all fundraising and public relations. Material from the department has been subdivided into four subseries (III.6-9) based on material type.
    This subseries, Subseries III.7, consists of memos, correspondence, notes, reports, drafts, and other administrative materials, created and/or kept by the Office of Development of Graham Windham. The Office of Development arranged the materials roughly by subject. Subjects are in no particular order. Subjects include memos regarding events and benefits (i.e. galas, alumni reunions), publications (i.e. annual report drafts, brochure drafts, public service announcements), Graham Windham sites (i.e. Hastings campus, Manhattan Center) and miscellaneous topics related to programs and services (i.e. adoption, volunteers). While most of the printed matter (brochures, etc.) kept by the Office of Development is in Subseries III.6, there is also a small amount interfiled with the materials in this subseries. Original folder titles have been maintained.
    Restricted materials have been separated to two boxes at the end of this subseries. Records in these last two boxes, Boxes 76 and 77, are closed to the public for a period of 100 years from the date of their creation.
    - 1990 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1991 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 1)
    - 1991 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1992 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 2)
    - 1991 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1992 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 3)
    - 1992 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1992 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Annual Report Material [draft materials], circa 1994 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1994 Annual Report Children's Stories [draft materials], circa 1995 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 6)
    - 1994 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1995 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 7)
    - 1994 Annual Report Copy [draft materials], circa 1995 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 8)
    - 1995 Annual Report [draft materials], circa 1996 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 1)
    - 1995 Annual Report [draft materials], circa 1996 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 2)
    - 1995 Annual Report [draft materials], circa 1996 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 3)
    - 1995 Annual Report [draft materials], circa 1996 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 4)
    - NAHC [National Association of Homes for Children] Questionnaire, 1991 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 5)
    - NAHC [National Association of Homes for Children] Directory Questionnaire, 1991 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 6)
    - NAHC [National Association of Homes for Children] Anniversary Publication, 1995 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 7)
    - NAHC [National Association of Homes for Children] Photo Contest GW Winner, 1995 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 8)
    - Adoption Recruitment - Mann. Hanover and Misc., 1991 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 9)
    - Adoption Recruitment Articles and Misc., 1991 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 10)
    - Adoption Flier, circa 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1)
    - Minority Families Adoption Recruitment Program, 1989 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 2)
    - Adoption Recruitment "Bank Book", 1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 3)
    - National Adoption Awareness Month, 1995 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 4)
    - Post Legal Adoption Program, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 5)
    - Foster Boarding Home, 1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 6)
    - Foster Care Resource Material, 1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 7)
    - Foster Parent Recognition Awards, 1996 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 8)
    - Project Welcome Home, 1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 9)
    - Welcome Home Project and Lipton Tea Company, 1990 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 10)
    - National Child Welfare League Scholarship Program (Freddie Mac), 1995 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 11)
    - Preventive Services Program, 1989 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 12)
    - "Cultivation" Events, 1989 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 1)
    - Foster Care and Family Day Care Providers Recognition Dinner, 1989 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 2)
    - WWRL Series, 1990 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 3)
    - Radio Stations Benefit Night, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 4)
    - GW Video, 1992 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 5)
    - Classic Black Event Benefit, 1992 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 6)
    - Kids' Poems for Gala, undated (Offsite-box 65, Folder 7)
    - Isabella Graham Award to Arthur Ashe, 1992 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 8)
    - Children Attend BAM Family Fun Series, 1990 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 9)
    - Staff Event at Gramercy Park Hotel, 1990 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 10)
    - Abbey Lincoln Concert Events, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 11)
    - Campus Dedication, 1991 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 12)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Opening, 1994 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 13)
    - Harlem Day Care Center Opening, 1994 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 14)
    - Nate Archibald Basketball Clinic, 1989 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Concert - 250th Anniversary of Handel's Messiah, 1990 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 2)
    - Holiday Events, 1990 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 3)
    - Jim Hensen Productions, 1991 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 4)
    - Johnson and Higgins Presentation, Holidays, 1991 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 5)
    - Tennis Tournament, 1991 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 6)
    - Art Gallery Benefit, Sculptor Vince Cordero, 1992 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 7)
    - Advocacy re: Budget Cuts, 1992 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 8)
    - Testimony re: State Budget, 1992 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 9)
    - Muppet Movie Premiere, 1992 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 10)
    - Letter re: possible visit of Hillary Clinton, 1992 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 11)
    - GW Crown Heights Health Fair, 1993 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 12)
    - City Budget "Lobby" Campaign, 1994 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 13)
    - Gracie Mansion Visit, 1994 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 14)
    - Rwanda Relief Programs, 1994 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Breakfast, 1995 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 16)
    - Staff Development Day - Early Childhood Services, 1995 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 17)
    - Mixed Basketball Clinic, 1996 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 18)
    - NAWBO Event, 1996 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 19)
    - Union 1199 Publicity, 1996 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 20)
    - Volunteer Activities for Kids, 1996 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 21)
    - Gala Benefit, 1994 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 1)
    - Journal Ads, 1999 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Gala Including Raffle (Offsite-box 67, Folder 3)
    - Kellogg's Account Management, J. Walter Thompson, 2000 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Gala Programs and Raffle (Offsite-box 67, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Award Winners, 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 6)
    - Events Including at School, 1998 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 7)
    - Great Adventure Trip, 1998 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 8)
    - Harlem Ministers Breakfast, 1998 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 9)
    - Staff Recognition Day, 1998 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Luncheon, 1999 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 11)
    - Staff Holiday Party, 2000 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 12)
    - 2001 Gala and Jazz Awards (Offsite-box 67, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1988 August 20 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1990 May 19 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1991 May 18 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1992 May 16 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1993 May 22 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1994 May 21 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1995 May 20 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1996 May 18 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1997 May 17 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1998 May 16 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Reunion, 1999 May 22 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 24)
    - Maps of Campus, undated (Offsite-box 68, Folder 1)
    - Campus Tree Lighting, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 2)
    - Wynton Marsalis Visit to Campus, 1989 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 3)
    - Tennis Courts Dedication, Arthur Ashe at Campus, 1989 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 4)
    - Campus Alumni, 1990 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Campus Activities, 1990 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 6)
    - Campus Tour - C. Ottley and Statistics, 1991 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Campus Activities, 1991 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Campus Activities, 1992 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 9)
    - Campus Brochure, 1992 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 10)
    - Graham School Student Testimonials, circa 2000-2010 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 11)
    - PSA [Public Service Announcement] Handbook, 1983 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 1)
    - NBC Spots re: Children Available for Adoption, 1990 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 2)
    - PSA [Public Service Announcement] Schedules, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 3)
    - Public Service Announcements, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 4)
    - Wynton Marsalis Public Service Announcement, 1990 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 5)
    - Alternative Housing Directory, 1989 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 6)
    - Neighborhood Family Service Center, Brooklyn, 1992 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 7)
    - GW School Children's Donations for Toy Drive/Yonkers YWCA, 1989 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 8)
    - Independent Living, 1990 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, Brooklyn Site, 1991 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 1)
    - Early Childhood Education Div. Programs, 1992 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 2)
    - GW Early Intervention Services - Preschool brochure, 1995 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 3)
    - GW Educational Services, undated (Offsite-box 70, Folder 4)
    - Finest Care Dedication, 1989 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 5)
    - Finest Day Care Program, circa 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 6)
    - Family Day Care Miscellaneous, 1991 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 7)
    - Community Foster Care Division, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 8)
    - Group Homes Project, 1992 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 9)
    - Grow with Us Program, 1990 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Child Care Award, 1996 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence re: GW as a Resource, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 1)
    - Graham Windham Mission Statement, 1991 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 2)
    - Early Childhood Services Handbook and Fliers, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 3)
    - Early Childhood Services Flipchart, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 4)
    - Board Manual, 1992 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 5)
    - Child Welfare Statistics Sheets, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 6)
    - Young Sisterhood Collective, 1992 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan Center Newsletter, 1989 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 8)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Printed Matter, 1993 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 9)
    - Bedford Refuge, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 1)
    - Environmental impact in Hastings of new pipeline on campus, 1994 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 2)
    - Finest Child Care Center anad Judith Dynia Mayor's Office, 1994 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 3)
    - Andrew Kerfut campus resident becomes Principal, 1996 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 4)
    - HR Fact Sheets, 1996 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 5)
    - New York's foster care system by Andrew Stein, NYC Council President, 1989 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 6)
    - Demographics by race and ethnicity, NYC, 1990 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 7)
    - Developmental Delay Research, 1990 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 8)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Information, 1990 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter contributions, 1989 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter resource file, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 11)
    - Big Apple Parents Paper, 1990 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 12)
    - Copy for ad in "Women's News" newspaper and recruitment leaflet, 1991 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 13)
    - GW Brochure, 1991 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 14)
    - Health Care Services Printed Matter, 1992 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 15)
    - NFSC Printed Matter, 1992 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 16)
    - Spring GW Record, 1997 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 17)
    - Harlem Child Care Insert, undated (Offsite-box 72, Folder 18)
    - CBS piece on adoption at campus, 1990 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 1)
    - Children's responses to WNBC program, "For Peace Sake", 1990 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 2)
    - Capital Campaign Breakfast and Miscellaneous, 1991 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 3)
    - Holiday Pitch Letters, 1991 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 4)
    - "In the Mix" Episode on GW and Foster Care, 1994 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 5)
    - Letters to Editors, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 6)
    - MAPP Information re: Foster Care, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 7)
    - Today Show WNBC-TV (Adoption), 1990 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 8)
    - NYU Story, 1991 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 9)
    - New York Women's Foundation Journal, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 10)
    - Testimonials Brochure, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 11)
    - Joyce Lapenn Op-Ed Piece in Newsday, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 12)
    - Pitch Letters, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 13)
    - Thank you letters - gifts under $100, 1990 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 14)
    - Children's Thank You Letters to Santa and Volunteers, 1995 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 15)
    - CWLA Testimony Before U.S. Senate, 1986 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 16)
    - United Way Profile of GW, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 17)
    - One-to-One and GW, 1992 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 18)
    - Copyright for Director for Child Welfare Field, 1989 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 1)
    - Statistics about New York City Children, 1993 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 2)
    - Human Sexuality: A CWA Curriculum, 1990 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 3)
    - American Red Cross Babysitting Course, 2005 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 4)
    - Beacon Center, 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 5)
    - Norman M. Segal re: Placement of Plaque in Memory of, 1992 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 6)
    - Beacon Mentoring Program, circa 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 7)
    - "Campus Culture" by Gerald S. Leventhal, 2002 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activities - General, 1993 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 9)
    - Advertisement Produced by J. Raniere, 1989 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 10)
    - Public Information Reports, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Teddy Bears Publicity, 1990 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 12)
    - Media Coverage and Relations, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 13)
    - Christmas and Rights "Because it's Christmas (for All Children)", 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 14)
    - Public Information Department Accomplishments, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 15)
    - MCI Toys for Tots, 1992 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 16)
    - Pro Bono Agencies, 1993 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 17)
    - Unicef Check Presentation - Rwanda Relief, 1994 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Letters to GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 19)
    - Human Interest Spots for Mother's Day, 1995 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 20)
    - "The Visionaries" TV Series, applying to, 1995 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 21)
    - 190th Anniversary Proclamation and Fundraising Strategies, 1996 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 22)
    - Radio Free Europe Interview of David Megley, undated (Offsite-box 74, Folder 23)
    - Volunteer Forms, 1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 1)
    - FBH Volunteer Activities, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 2)
    - Volunteers - Misc., 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 3)
    - GW Steel Band Engagements including United Nations, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 4)
    - Memorandum of Understanding between GW and Pace University re: Volunteers, 1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 5)
    - Yankees Game Excursion - Rye Friends, 1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Friends, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 7)
    - May Taylor Day, 1995 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 8)
    - Spring Cleaning - Bronxville High School Graduating Class Helps GW Children, 1996 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 9)
    - Several Board Members: Hall, Clutz, Wallace, Tarry, Kendrick, Dwyer, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 1)
    - Board Chair Michael Ainslie, circa 1989-1996 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 2)
    - Board Profiles, 1996 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 3)
    - Board Member Suzanne F. Ainslie, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 4)
    - Board Member Suzanne Frutig Bales, 1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 5)
    - Board Member Susan S. Bohen, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 6)
    - Board Member Barbard Carr, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 7)
    - Board Member John Cecil, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 8)
    - Board Member Denise Crimmins Clayton, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 9)
    - Board Member Patricia F. Dunning, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 10)
    - Board Member Robert Ferrari, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 11)
    - Board Member Bruce S. Fowle, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 12)
    - Board Member Lorraine Friedman, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 13)
    - Board Member Thomas E. Greene, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 14)
    - Board Member Michael Golden, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 15)
    - Board Member Pamela L. Goldman, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 16)
    - Board Member James J. Nicholson, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 17)
    - Board Member Sydney Reynolds, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 18)
    - Board Member Elizabeth Sargent, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 19)